[SPEAKER_00]: Okay, so there was something that caused it to not go down far enough.
[SPEAKER_00]: to actually, there's some kind of situation.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's a push pull.
[SPEAKER_00]: So like a push bar comes down just like a pulling out.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: But that push bar is something that tripped the machine.
[SPEAKER_00]: to where it wasn't all the way flush.
[SPEAKER_00]: And I don't remember what cause.
[SPEAKER_00]: It's very, very rare, but some cause.
[SPEAKER_00]: Just some scrap or something could have been in the way.
[SPEAKER_00]: Well it floated over, the push bar floated over.
[SPEAKER_00]: and pull the other sheet on top of it.
[SPEAKER_00]: So there was two sheets, two sheets.
[SPEAKER_00]: And the operator was not there.
[SPEAKER_00]: It was break time, but he was the one supposed to be on it, and he was in the bathroom.
[SPEAKER_00]: Do they let him run?
[SPEAKER_00]: And then what happened?
[SPEAKER_00]: It started to cut the next program with an inch and a half of material on the table.
[SPEAKER_00]: So it was burying the collet.
[SPEAKER_00]: the spindle head and just pulling like catching things on fire.
[SPEAKER_00]: It doesn't sound good
[SPEAKER_00]: And they were like, we don't need an evac system, let's just walk out of the building.
[SPEAKER_00]: I'll never forget that.
[SPEAKER_00]: I was sitting there like... I was like...
[SPEAKER_00]: Where are all those people walking outside?
[SPEAKER_00]: I guess the office people are just dying of fire.
[SPEAKER_00]: Cause ain't no one trippin' before I mark two to people who haven't had enough.
[SPEAKER_00]: That's the only time that I remember that we ever really needed it.
Yeah.
[SPEAKER_00]: Yeah.